Guide to the Student Organization Records
University of Houston Libraries
- Tau Beta Sigma
  - Files
    - Wedding Napkin & Program, Becky & John, September 20, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Photos arranged alphabetically
    - Allen, Meghan (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Arnold, Tracie (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Atkinson, Stephanie (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Bennett, Ricky (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - Bishop, Scott (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Bland, John (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - Brown, Tiffany (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - Browning, Raylena (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - Buchanan, Staci (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - Burch, Kelly (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - Cabrito (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - Chinni, Chris (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - Collins, Stephanie (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - Copeland, Cara (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - Cottrell, Louis (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - Crofoot, Casey (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - Cushing, Matthew (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - Dacey, Kevin (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - Daly, Sean (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - Davidson, Rayhni (Box 6, Folder 67)
    - DeBardelaben, Becky (Box 6, Folder 68)
    - DeJesus, Kevin (Box 6, Folder 69)
    - De Las Santos, Jeff, “Jesus” (Box 6, Folder 70)
    - Doucette, Kristi (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - Duham, Lonnie (Box 6, Folder 72)
    - Easterling, Shelia (Box 6, Folder 73)
    - Egg (Box 6, Folder 74)
    - Enax, Lezli (Box 6, Folder 75)
    - Flinn, Mike (Box 6, Folder 76)
    - Flores, Tony (Box 6, Folder 77)
    - Foster, Jason, “Oscar” (Box 6, Folder 78)
    - Frank, Jason (Box 6, Folder 79)
    - Friedrich, Jeffrey (Box 6, Folder 80)
    - Funk, Chris (Box 6, Folder 81)
    - Garcia, Lynn (Box 6, Folder 82)
    - Gardner, Teri (Box 6, Folder 83)
    - Gometz, Joann (Box 6, Folder 84)
    - Gore, Gaby (Box 6, Folder 85)
    - Gunn, Laura (Box 6, Folder 86)
    - Guzman, Johnny (Box 6, Folder 87)
    - Hadden, Carole (Box 6, Folder 88)
    - Hamilton, Kristen (Box 6, Folder 89)
    - Harrington, Sarah (Box 6, Folder 90)
    - Harris, Amy (Box 6, Folder 91)
    - Heidt, Aimee (Box 6, Folder 92)
    - Hill, Jenny (Box 6, Folder 93)
    - Hinman, Valerie (Box 6, Folder 94)
    - Jamez, Damon (Box 6, Folder 95)
    - Ann Janik, Lee (Box 6, Folder 96)
    - Jimenez, Delma (Box 6, Folder 97)
    - Joanna (Box 6, Folder 98)
    - Johnson, Missy (Box 6, Folder 99)
    - Jone, Mike, “Band Fan” (Box 6, Folder 100)
    - Jordan, Dustin (Box 6, Folder 101)
    - Jordan, Greg (Box 6, Folder 102)
    - Khoury, Elise (Box 6, Folder 103)
    - Klenke, Chad (Box 6, Folder 104)
    - Lambrecht, Chris (Box 6, Folder 105)
    - Lanehart, Shauna (Box 6, Folder 106)
    - Lauche, Hans (Box 6, Folder 107)
    - Laughlin, Clark (Box 6, Folder 108)
    - Lazenby, Jennifer (Box 6, Folder 109)
    - Lazenby, Stacy (Box 6, Folder 110)
    - Lee, Tina (Box 6, Folder 111)
    - Lively, Nikki & (Ringo) (Box 6, Folder 112)
    - Lundberg, Michael (Box 6, Folder 113)
    - Maher, Eddie (Box 6, Folder 114)
    - Mammiga, Kevin (Box 6, Folder 115)
    - Mammiga, Sara (Box 6, Folder 116)
    - Markley, Angela (Box 6, Folder 117)
    - Martin, Sarah (Box 6, Folder 118)
    - Mayes, Mr. (Box 6, Folder 119)
    - Mayes, Mrs (Box 6, Folder 120)
    - Montemayor, Javier (Box 6, Folder 121)
    - Montgomery, Sandy (Box 6, Folder 122)
    - Moody, Adam (Box 6, Folder 123)
    - Moore, Merideth (Box 6, Folder 124)
    - Nair, Preeter (Box 6, Folder 125)
    - Newman, Stephanie (Box 6, Folder 126)
    - Newman, Scott & (Ringo) (Box 6, Folder 127)
    - Nunẻ̃z, Joe (Box 6, Folder 128)
    - Ocãnas, Pablo (Box 6, Folder 129)
    - Parker, Devin (Box 6, Folder 130)
    - Patterson, Chris (Box 6, Folder 131)
    - Plagens, Jeff (Box 6, Folder 132)
    - Prexel, Joanna (Box 6, Folder 133)
    - Ramirez, Laura (Box 6, Folder 134)
    - Ramsell, Amy (Box 6, Folder 135)
    - Rangel, Pete (Box 6, Folder 136)
    - Ratner, Jacob (Box 6, Folder 137)
    - Remmert, Jason (Box 6, Folder 138)
    - Ricon, Ramon (Box 6, Folder 139)
    - Ringo, John (Box 6, Folder 140)
    - Robinett, Suzy (Box 6, Folder 141)
    - Robinson, Stewart (Box 6, Folder 142)
    - Rusch, Mark (Box 6, Folder 143)
    - Shultz, Skip (Box 6, Folder 144)
    - Scott, Chris (Box 6, Folder 145)
    - Shin, Matt (Box 6, Folder 146)
    - Skelly, Tanya (Box 6, Folder 147)
    - Smith, Carl (Box 6, Folder 148)
    - Smith, Tim (Box 6, Folder 149)
    - Tank (Box 6, Folder 150)
    - Thomas, JR (Box 6, Folder 151)
    - Tiffany (Box 6, Folder 152)
    - Tisnabudi, Irson (Box 6, Folder 153)
    - Tonneson, Scott (Box 6, Folder 154)
    - Turner, Raymond (Box 6, Folder 155)
    - Van Wyk, Amy (Box 6, Folder 156)
    - Vann, Joe (Box 6, Folder 157)
    - Villareal, Lisa (Box 6, Folder 158)
    - Vince (Box 6, Folder 159)
    - Wessale, Dana (Box 6, Folder 160)
    - Williams, Marvin (Box 6, Folder 161)
    - Winson, Dustin (Box 6, Folder 162)
    - Young, Anthony (Box 6, Folder 163)
    - Tubans Love Meat!!! (Box 6, Folder 164)
  - Photos arranged by date
    - undated (Box 7, Folder 1-4)
    - Recruiting, undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - 1980 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - District VI Convention, Spring 1980 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - 1985 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Spring Formal, May 16, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Spring Banquet, May 16, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Mixer, Fall 1988 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Hawaii, Fall 1988 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Pledge Class, Fall 1988 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous, Spring 1988 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Baylor, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Homecoming 1988, Kevin Borgfel, Honorary TBE (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Pledge Recital Practice, Spring 1988 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Cougar Brass, Spring 1988 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Wedding Barbee Ruppel’s, Summer 1988 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Induction, “The Pea”, Fall 1988 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Drum Majors, Robbie Melinder, & Kevin Borgfeld, Fall 1988 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Summer Band, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Marching Rehearsal, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Oilers' Game, Fall 1988 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - SWC Tournament, Spring 1989 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Band Banquet, Fall 1989 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Summer Band, Fall 1989 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Spring Formal, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Induction, Fuddruckers, Fall 1989 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Football Games, Fall 1989 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Induction, Spring 1989 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Spring, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Wind Ensemble Concert, Spring 1989 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - TBE Appreciation Dinner, Spring 1989 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Solo Ensemble, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Garage Sale, Spring 1989 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - October 1989 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Wrapping KKY Room, Spring 1999 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Games, Fall 1990 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Service Project, Fall 1990 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Formal, Spring 1990 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Photos from Beta Chapter at Texas Tech, Fall 1990 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Pledge ship, Spring 1991 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Formal, Spring 1990 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - SW District Convention, Spring 1991 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Induction Dinner Fuddruckers, Spring 1991 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Band, Summer 1991 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Fall 1991 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Wind Ensemble II Concert, Spring 1992 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Recital, Spring 1992 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Formal, Spring 1992 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 52-54)
    - Spring 1992 (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - Fall 1992 (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - Spring 1993 (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - 1994 (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - Winter Retreat, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 59)
    - Fall 1995 (Box 7, Folder 60-61)
    - Spring 1995 (Box 7, Folder 62-63)
    - Recital, Hell Week, Spring 1995 (Box 7, Folder 64)
    - Spring 1996 (Box 7, Folder 65)
    - Fall 1996 (Box 7, Folder 66)
    - Spring 1997 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Slides
    - Slides, undated (Box 8, Folder 1-3)
  - Negatives
    - Negatives, undated (Box 8, Folder 4-16)
    - National Convention, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Band Day, Fall 1986/1988 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - SWC Tourny, Spring 1987 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Packing for Hawaii, December 1988 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Induction, “The Pea”, Fall 1988 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - KKY Smorg, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Christmas Party, Robb Ripley’s apt., Fall 1988 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Football Game & Seniors, Fall 1988 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Fall 1988 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Homecoming, “Ride the Tide of Cougar Pride”, vs. TCU, Fall 1988 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - 1st Degree Dinner, Fall 1988 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Baylor Game, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Summer 1988 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Hawaii, Fall 1988 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - District Sam Houston, Spring 1988 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Cougar Kick-off Doug King, Fall 1988 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Getting Ready for Final, Fall 1988 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Packing for Hawaii, Fall 1988 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Initiation Dinner at Gator’s, Fall 1988 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Solo and Ensemble, Spring 1988 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Cougar Brass, Spring 1989 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Cougar Brass, Spring 1989 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - KKY Retreat Annex, Spring 1989 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Slumber Party, Spring 1989 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Formal, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Football Game, Fall 1989 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - National Convention, OSU, Summer 1989 (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Induction Fudruckers, Fall 1989 (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Football Games, Fall 1989 (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Wind Ensemble Concert, Spring 1989 (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - TBE Appreciation Dinner & Getting ready for District, Spring 1989 (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - Profiles-Melissa Wiglie, May 21, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - Spring 1991 (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - Summer Band, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - Spring Formal (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - Initiation Dinner, Olive Garden, Fall 1992 (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - Bowling Rush, Fall 1992 (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - Halloween Party, Karen Holmes House, Fall 1992 (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - Formal Rush, Bira Poretti’s, Fall 1992 (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - Sorority Football, Fall 1992 (Box 8, Folder 56)
    - Recital & Recital Dinner, Black Eyed Peas, Fall 1992 (Box 8, Folder 57)
    - Football Games, Fall 1992 (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - Slumber Rush, Beth Wooster’s Apt., Fall 1992 (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - 60 D’Juana East and Joe Munez Wedding, May 15, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - Solo & Ensemble Spring, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 61)
    - Annex Cleaning, Turnabout day, Fall 1992 (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - Mixer, Alan Starfield’s House, Fall 1992 (Box 8, Folder 63)
    - Induction, Fudruckers, Fall 1992 (Box 8, Folder 64)
    - Christmas Party, Denise McGills House, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 65)
    - Homecoming, Fall 1992 (Box 8, Folder 66)
    - Senior Football Game, Fall 1992 (Box 8, Folder 67)
    - Spring, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 68)
    - Induction Dinner Fudruckers, Spring 1993 (Box 8, Folder 69)
    - KKY/TBE, Southwest District Convention, Houston, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 70)
    - Summer Band 1993, Hall Party, 1993, Rush, Fall 1993 (Box 8, Folder 71)
    - Summer Band, August 1994 (Box 8, Folder 72)
    - Summer Service Project, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 73)
    - Initiation Fall, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 74)
    - Summer Band, Fall 1994 (Box 8, Folder 75)
    - Rehearsal, Wind and The Lion Shaft, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 76)
    - Cougar Kickoff, Fall 1994 (Box 8, Folder 77)
    - Induction, The Weenie, Fall 1994 (Box 8, Folder 78)
    - Cleaning Day, Fall 1994 (Box 8, Folder 79)
    - Spring 1995 (Box 8, Folder 80)
    - Negatives, Fall 1995 (Box 8, Folder 81)
    - At A&M, Fall 1995 (Box 8, Folder 82)
    - At Rice, Fall 1995 (Box 8, Folder 83)
    - Recital/Hell Week, Spring 1995 (Box 8, Folder 84)
    - TCU, Fall 1995 (Box 8, Folder 85)
    - Pledge ship, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 86)
    - Spring, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 87)
    - Spring, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 88)
    - Fall 1996 (Box 8, Folder 89)
    - Spring 1997 (Box 8, Folder 90)
    - Spring 1997 (Box 8, Folder 91)
    - Sisters of TAU (Box 8, Folder 92)
    - Work Project (Box 8, Folder 93)
  - Scrapbooks
    - Spring 1981 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Fall 1980 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Spring 1980 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Academic Year, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Academic Year, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Green scrapbook (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Blue scrapbook (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Red scrapbook, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Beige scrapbook, UH Cougar Marching Band (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - TBS poster (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Memorabilia
    - Band Buttons, undated (Box 10, Item 1)
    - Cloth Band People Puppets & Flag, undated (Box 11, Item 1)
    - Pillow and Binder (Box 12, Item 1)
- Council of Ethnic Organizations (CEO) Unprocessed 2011 Additions
  Scope and Contents
  This series consists of 11 unprocessed boxes containing records transferred from the Council of Ethnic Orgnizations.
- Center for Student Involvement (CSI) unprocessed 2014 additions, 1956-2014
  This series consists of 28 unprocessed boxes containing records relating to the Center for Student Involvement (CSI) and the fee-funded student organizations it oversees. There is also one OVS folder.
  - Bands of America: Southwest Regional, 1989 (Drawer F.9, Ovs folder 6)
    Photograph
- Center for Fraternity and Sorority Life (CFSL) Unprocessed 2014 Additions, 1951-2007
  This series consists of 1 unprocessed box containing documents, slides and audio tapes relating to the Center for Fraternity and Sorority Life (CFSL) and the fraternities and sororities it supports.